(Raj:)So, I'd like
to try a technique
(Raj:)where no one gets steamrolled.
(Raj:)When you talk,
(Raj:)instead of bringing up
a new idea, respect what was
(Raj:)just said by building on it.
(Sheldon:)Uh, building on that...
Mm-hmm.
(Sheldon:)...we should order dinner.
(Leonard:)How is that building
on what he just said?
(Howard:)Building on what Sheldon said,
I could go for Chinese.
(Howard:)Hang on.
Building on what Leonard said,
(Raj:)no one built on what I said.
Building on "building on that,"
(Sheldon:)there's a new build-your-own
pizza place on Colorado.
(Sheldon:)Building on that,
I'd like to remind you,
(Leonard:)I'm lactose intolerant.
(Howard:)I saw the menu.
They have soy cheese.
Ha, ha! You didn't say
"building on." You're out!
(Leonard:)It's not Simon Says.
(Raj:)Yeah, you're missing
the point, Sheldon.
You're out, and you're out.
I win! Who wants pizza?
(Girl:)Penny?
(Penny:)Oh, hey.
Hey.
(Girl:)I haven't seen you
auditioning in a while.
(Penny:)Yeah, uh, I got a job
as a pharmaceutical sales rep.
(Girl:)You quit acting?
Well, kind of.
(Penny:)But now I get to act like